Engage with God
VIEWER'S PRAYER
Viewers, wherever you are, whatever position you are in,
are you on the sickbed?
Whatever medium you are using to view us,
once you are under the influence of this voice, begin to release yourself, in the name of Jesus!
You are created to lead!
Begin to lead, in the name of Jesus!
In every area of your life, begin to lead, in the name of Jesus!
You are created to lead!
Begin to lead, in the name of Jesus!
Greater is He!
It is not less is He; it is greater is He!
This is why I command that spirit of leader!
You will lead others, in the name of Jesus!
Begin to lead others, in the name of Jesus!
In your business, begin to lead others, in the name of Jesus!
In your finances, begin to lead others, in the name of Jesus!
In your career, begin to lead others, in the name of Jesus!
Lead, in the name of Jesus!
Right now, begin to confess your freedom, your triumph!
Confess your triumph!
Confess your victory!
Viewers, your health - be restored, in the name of Jesus!
If there is anywhere, any area, any faculty, any organ that is sick,
be healed, in the name of Jesus!
Be it your kidney, your blood, your liver, your heart, every organ - be healed!
Be restored!
By the power of the Holy Ghost, by the blood of Jesus!
Holy Ghost!
Rejoice!
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing the World!
RV: Mel Flowers 06/04/2019